All of us, dream save us!
All of us !All
of us Heart looking
I'm glad you got some guts, cause
you couldn't run if you wanted to!
Hakugan!
Get to the Polar Tank!
Roger!
Chouchou, Peguin, into the sea!
Leave it to us!
Free room, go!
What the hell?
Amputate!
was that an awakened technique when did
you learn to do that yes you did it captain
No, not yet.
Drinking bastard!
You picked your spider!
Ha ha ha ha!
River Cry!
He's a monster!
Say it ain't so strong,
you were taken too soon,
oh cool, he's galloping through
heaven now, payback time.
Hey, look up!
Something's falling!
Everybody run!
The apples are bombs!
Nah.
We were born and raised at the coldest
part in the north blow, you know.
You may be tough, but there's
no way you can beat us at sea.
We're about to sink your ship.
Prepare to attack!
Oh, John Barr, three o 'clock,
a sniper, get ready to block,
I'm on it,
interesting,
his
defenses may prove hard
to break, K-Room, go.
Who was that supposed to hurt, you idiot?
Shock feeler.
Hmm, predictable.
You can't just charge
in without a strategy.
Now, warp.
Avador, would you like
to return to the ship?
You kidding me?
I'm just getting started here.
Very well, then. Warp!
It's Blackbeard!
All your top officers
have Devil Fruit powers.
That means all your best fighters
are weak against the sea.
After seeing the kind of power we've
got, you don't think that's a fair trade.
Vroom, go!
Tuck!
K. Roo!
Enemy attack from the world!
Bastards are trying to sink on ship!
How the hell are they this strong at sea?
This is wild!
All they're doing is shaking us
around a bit, and it won't last long.
No one in the world can
stand up against our comedy.
If Mama is still alive, she won't
be talking that way much longer.
If she's alive, we're fighting the
guy who killed her right now. Wow!
That old bat and her era are as dead
as your hopes of getting out of here!
A short time ago on Kaku Island,
two intruders suddenly appeared in
Chocolat Town, where pudding resided.
the goal of the intruders
was to abduct pudding they
were from the blackbeard
pirates one was the longtime
member van ogre the other
was kuzan i know what you're
expecting but if you think
you If you can force my hand,
you're mistaken.
You'll never get what you want.
Reports say that Blackbeard
and Trafalgar Law
are clashing at Winter
Island in the New World.
That's the problem with
being Fleet Admiral.
I have to sit here and wait
instead of wringing their necks.
Okay, that was weird, but I
think we're in the clear now.
Jeez body if you made
me any older my bones
would have turned to
dust when I fell down.
I get why you're upset, but
pacifistas are dangerous.
And there's lots of them, so you better get
used to watching us beat your dad's ass.
I'm sorry.
Luffy, that's enough.
I know this is hard, Bonnie.
I really do.
But we've dealt with pacifistas in
the past, so just trust us, okay?
Also, if it's not too much trouble,
please turn me back before I die.
I should have thought of this.
Kuma was a normal human before they
started cloning him, after all.
Of course he'd have a family out there.
Let me get something
straight with you, Bonnie.
Please don't be offended,
but I heard that Kuma was the
wicked king of the Sorbet Kingdom,
who was expelled by its
people and became a pirate.
Later, he joined up with
the Revolutionary Army,
but was arrested by the Navy
and sentenced to life in prison.
But Dr.
Vegapunk took an interest in him He
saw potential in his unique physiology.
And so Kuma was allowed to return to
the seas as one of the seven warlords.
But he had to agree to cloning
and body augmentation too!
Is that correct?
The warlord part and the cloning
part do make sense to me.
But the cyborg part, that's
like a death sentence!
No one would agree to have their
whole mind taken away like that?
I don't know his crimes, so I don't
know what kind of deal he agreed to.
But they called him Kuma the Tyrant
and gave him a life sentence.
That's a lie!
My dad wasn't a tyrant!
And I'm positive that he
hated the world government.
He'd never help them by choice.
They did these things
to him against his will!
Are you trying to kill us?
You know I can't move fast anymore!
But that weapon was pretty cool, huh?
Bless my bones!
Was that a beam saver?
There isn't much that works here.
All these must be rejected inventions.
But this one's good.
Vegapunk has to pay.
He committed murder in
the name of science!
My father said he came from
a special race of people.
Fine, so what?
That doesn't give people the
right to experiment on him.
That doesn't give them the
right to erase his mind, yeah.
Tell him: a special race, huh?
Bonnie, you forgot to turn me back.
It can fly!
You gotta make us one of these, Franky!
So cool!
Vegaforce One is propelled
by the jets on its back,
but it's kept afloat by
an anti-gravity device.
Oh Tang, that sounds sweet!
It's only possible because of
the air regulation on the island,
but I want to take it worldwide.
Whoa, a city! It's huge!
I've never seen architecture
like that before.
And up we go!
Hey, look!
There's a giant monster down there!
Oh, man, this is amazing!
And another giant robot!
How many they got?
Franky, Franky, Franky!
Check out the flying fish!
They have anti-gravity devices too.
It's straight out of the sci-fi story.
You bet it is.
We specialize in building the future here
This is the future island.
Above the clouds is the
laboratory level lab, a phase.
Below is the factory level, fabrio phase.
That's for all the workers and
researchers live your captains down there,
breaking stuff like a
caveman in a cryo center.
I'm glad to know he's all right.
All right, we're here!
What kind of cool stuff
are we gonna see next?
Hey, what gives?
Aren't you guys coming?
We gotta go!
I'm on ship watch. Me as well.
Can't take risks.
I don't trust that woman.
Course not, you're an asshole.
Don't listen to him, Lilith!
We all think you're great!
Uh-huh? What is it?
Try it and see.
You mean just step on it?
It's just like Skypiea!
Yep!
Ooh, I wanna try!
Me too, me too!
This is awesome!
I thought it really takes me back!
This is the first time for
me, but I'm digging it!
I wish I could've been there!
Soon did Vegapunk make
these clouds, too? Uh-huh.
Not too shabby, right?
You can probably tell, but by
controlling the island's air systems,
I was able to modify
the density of pyrobroin
and water vapor in the
condensation nuclei.
and recreate the island clouds
and sea clouds of Skypiea.
Those have got to be made up words.
And this is the entrance to the lab!
Awesome!
It's huge!
You'll need to put on research
suits before you go in.
There are changing rooms through
the Trinko's on the sides.
Welcome.
Please choose your
preferred clothing style.
Okay, but how do I do that?
It's touching me!
Pull the levers on your Dom
shoes to adjust the size.
They'll fit any type of foot.
These things, right?
I don't know, they look pretty bulky.
Oh, they're so light!
Oh!
And adorable!
Wow, that's a killer look, Robin! Love it!
So these clothes can reshape?
I bet they could strangle us to death.
Why would you even say that?
Oh, yeah!
Future Usopp coming through!
Vegapunk is the man!
His clothes even fit cyborgs!
Super!
Mine's just a normal Aloha shirt.
But who cares about me?
You ladies look nice!
It's different, but it's comfy.
You look ready to kick ass,
Robin! Do I? How about me?
You look like a perv in any outfit.
You're making me blush!
Some say that foresight
is a genius's blessing.
Though I'm inclined to call it a curse.
You know I can't stand it when
you're talking riddles, Vegapunk.
Then I'll be frank.
I'm going to die soon.
What are you talking about?
Is that supposed to be a joke?
I just wanted you to
know before it happens.
Goodbye, dragon.
So, why didn't you go
along with the others?
I'm on standby to go rescue them.
It's a government island.
They're probably walking into a trap.
You know, I had the exact same thought.
Now, would you care for some tea?
Sure. Thanks, pal.
Excuse me, good sirs?
Why are you still here? Whoa! Wait!
Don't be so cruel!
I know the deal was that you'd give
me a ride anywhere outside of Wano,
but I can't get off here!
As you said, it's a government island!
I'm not exactly welcome!
I appreciate you helping out our captain.
But we're done. Get lost. Oh! Oh! Oh!
You're gonna pay for this someday!
Ew!
The stairs move?
Hell yeah!
So, riding these stairs in style!
Like climbing a zone yesterday!
The steps are pouring out from the ground!
This is so crazy!
How does this thing work?
What's it run on?
Everything on the island
is powered by fire.
Flames can be converted
to all forms of energy.
So you need natural resources?
I've done a lot of research on what
matter is most efficient to burn.
But what I really want is an
undying flame so I can make a sun!
Make a sun!
You're walking into a wall!
Open the wall, thingy!
Just walk through it like I did!
Trust your brains, not your eyes.
Lewis! Lewis!
Why are you yelling, Edison?
Let live, my evil queen!
Huh?
I can't hear anything.
Did she leave us?
The man isn't gone!
I wouldn't worry.
If he had really been decapitated,
there'd be blood everywhere.
Thank you for that absolutely
terrifying analysis!
Sanji, you still alive? I'm fine.
You can just walk right through.
I better not break my
nose. Let me try. Huh?
Neat!
Not you, too! Bye, Uffar.
I passed through.
But how?
Geez, why are you trying to confuse me?
It's totally solid when
you go through! Why?
How does this even work?
Wait, where did Lilith go?
Hello?
Walk straight ahead.
Who's there?
Oh, I'm Vegapunk Ed, at your service.
Welcome to the lab.
I'll guide you from here.
Keep going.
I don't think I'm ever going
to figure out this weird place.
I'm going to hunt for
some future treasure.
What would that be exactly?
Like pretty, pretty flowers made of money.
Are you a little princess
or a greedy old bag?
Future Kitsch!
Future Bane!
Someone's been there.
What? Hold up! No way!
It's Jinbei!
It can't be. He's too young.
And he looks different somehow.
Okay, the first option,
this is Jinbei's child.
Hmm, second option, Jinbei
was turned into a child.
I don't think so.
Third option, he's a look-alike,
with wings, and a really weird vibe.
Hey, who are you?
He's big.
He might look like a kid, but
he's as tall as the real Jinbei.
I got a bad feeling about this.
Option four is a pacifista!
We gotta get out of here!
I knew this had to be a
government trap, I just knew it!
Jinbei, stop it!
He doesn't seem to recall
that name, or any of us.
Well, it was worth a shot, but
I guess he's not our friend.
Jinbei aside, this still feels wrong.
Sure, he's kinda big, but
he looks like a kid to me!
What?
Devil Fruit powers!
What the hell?
I'm ready to go, Nami.
Are we doing this? Not yet. Hold on.
Wait, I know that power,
but how did he get it too?
Stop it! Let her go!
Jin... Jinbei!
I said let her go, you bastard!
I don't want to throw hands, but I will
mess you up, even if Vegapunk is my hero!
Death penalty it is.
Whether you're Jinbei or
not, I'm gonna make you pay!
I'll show you no mercy.
You've made an enemy of us.
Kigan de Gro!
Sea Serpent, Snap Dragon!
Space!
Robin, get back!
That's Fishman Karate!
Hey, special attack, green
star, skull bomb, grass.
Get it together, Usopp, you can do this.
He's not the real Jinbei.
Did you get him?
Yeah, I think he's down.
He's gone.
Oh, come on.
I missed?
How could I miss?
He was right there!
No! Stay away!
Let go of me!
I'm coming! Stay back!
I got this one!
Usopp, stand perfectly still!
Dammit!
Let me go!
You gotta stand still, bro!
I can't take the shot!
What is this energy he's using?
It can't be.
Radical!
S-Shark, dodge now! B!
He can shoot lasers?
What kind of pirate shoots lasers?
If that had hit S-Shark, it
would have been a catastrophe.
The Seraphim are still children.
They're not ready for laser tests yet.
Ow, what the fulcrum?
Who does that idiot think he is
shooting up our expensive stuff?
I'm gonna rip his head
off and put it in a jar.
All right, too evil.
What, you want me to
be nice to the pirates?
Those rats are gonna die in the slab.
Way too evil.
Come on, S-Shark, time to
beat them into the ground.
Activate murder mode! Oh, no!
No murder mode!
Trust me, I have more than
enough test data to...
Eureka!
I just thought of a new invention!
Oh, nice work, buddy.
You go do your thing.
I'll hold down the fort for you.
I'm leaving you in charge.
The backer is safe!
What?
All over it, pal.
Data like this is my
morning cup of coffee.
I must draw the blueprints post-haste.
So much work to be done.
Come, my sis-tubby!
Sweet ontogenesis!
Unbelievable!
The Seraphim's attack patterns are
continuing to develop as he grows!
As I hypothesized, it seems that experiences
are stored in their bloodline elements.
Go!
Get those pirates out!
Come on, S-Shark!
Look at him go.
Oh, they evolve into war machines so fast.
Heart rate of 90, and his green
blood concentration went up.
Show them who's top of the food chain!
Let chum out of those chumps!
A cursed stomach!
Why must you rumble so?
These revelations are too important.
I don't have time to take a lunch break.
Quick, eat something for me, York!
Yay!
York! Sweet nutrition!
It's sucking into my brain!
The idea sprints first anew!
Eat your cake!
We brought everything
we could grab! Eat up!
Oh, come on, what am I, dieting?
Bring more, please, and thank you!
Oh, yes, ma 'am! Right away!
This is life.
BMI is over 600. I'll repeat.
BMI is over 600.
Oh, relax.
I was done anyway.
Keep it going, shark.
New battle data keeps pouring
in by the second. Huh?
Oh, oh.
No.
No, no, no, no, no.
Oh, let's call a temporary choice!
No, this is no time to drop an adritus!
Come on, bells!
Can't you see I'm busy?
Much better!
Digestion patch!
It's this!
Now for the experimental phase!
Bring me all the data we
have on Devil Fruit powers.
Bring Devil Fruit data to Pythagoras!
Prepare for an endless experiment!
To Situation Room 88!
Sleepy.
The day is an over and
York is on her board.
Eat, go, sleep!
Hold up, what's going on with my feet?
Seraphim, abort all attack operations.
Edison, Lilith, Pythagoras.
Your experiment is over.
Oh, there goes my name.
No!
It's more just kidding, it's a good part.
Stupid Killjoy!
Eureka!
I don't know what happened, but
I think that guy just saved us.
Whoever he is, I don't trust him one bit.
He must be the guy Lilith
was talking to. No way!
Could he be?
I am Dr.
Vegapunk, Shaka the Good.
Another Vegapunk?
Not overdoing it, don't you think?
So, you are the famous Straw
Hat Crew. Yeah, pleasure.
Now can you tell us why our
shoes are stuck to the floor?
Dom's shoes are magnetized.
We can control them
remotely inside the lab.
Resistance is futile, I take it.
I cannot trust pirates.
Okay, but are you really Dr. Vegapunk?
Because you're like the
third one we met today.
Indeed.
We are all Vegapunk.
What does that mean?
How many Vegapunks are there?
Am I Vegapunk? What?
No, bro, will you stop embarrassing me?
Tell me, does this island
look like the future to you?
What?
Are you kidding me?
Of course it does!
You got mechanical
monsters out at the sea.
Vegaforce One flying around.
Air and temperature
regulations everywhere.
this place looks like the super future!
The city here is like nothing
I've ever seen before.
I want to check out that
tech from top to bottom.
This island's the freaking ball.
So don't be a hater, Vangapro.
Let us go explore it. Pretty please.
It will never surpass its predecessor.
This island is the past.
How could you call it the past?
Hypothetically speaking, if I told
you there was an advanced kingdom,
much like this island, that existed
900 years ago, would you believe me?
Wait, like 9-0-0?
That's crazy talk, bro!
Chopper, look!
It's really real, it's not a hop of it!
Gotta come check this out!
See that?
It's metal!
Looks impressive, but it's pretty beat up.
Do you think this thing
used to move around?
Well, that would be a stretch,
even with this Isla's tech.
It looks like it's quite old.
Can we ride it? Yeah! Great idea!
I'll reach into the...
Thank you.